shoemoney.net 2017-05-30

# BlogNinja - Learn Internet Marketing

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OR ACCESSING ANY PART OF THE WEBSITE OR ITS SERVICES.**

**OVERVIEW**

Blog Ninja, Inc. and ShoeMoney Media Group, Inc. (collectively referred to as "Blog Ninja," “us,” or “we”) respect the privacy of users of Blog Ninja's websites http://shoemoney.net and http://blogninja.com and the websites' services (the website and services are collectively referred to as the "Services"). The following privacy policy (the "Policy") tells you about the information that Blog Ninja collects through the Services and how Blog Ninja may use or disclose that collected information. 

By accessing the Services, continuing to access the Services, or submitting any information through the Services, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us, as described below. Your use of the Services is also governed by the Terms of Service, which are expressly incorporated into this Policy. 

**UPDATES**

Blog Ninja reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time, and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy. Blog Ninja will not notify the Services' users of any such changes by email or other personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit the Services so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Blog Ninja does not intend to use the Services to collect any information from children under age 13. By submitting any information through the Services, you represent and warrant that you are 13 years of age or older. 

Blog Ninja may collect and store any information you submit or upload through the Services, whether through your account registration, uploading of user content, filling out a survey, posting of comments, or otherwise. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, contact information, personal preferences, payment information, or any other information submitted by you or any user through the Services. 

Blog Ninja may collect information about you from third-parties, including any third parties with whom you interact through your completion of the Blog Ninja network tasks. Blog Ninja may aggregate any information about you collected from any source. 

Blog Ninja may also collect passive information about your visit or use of the Services, including the date and time of your visit, the length of your visit, the specific webpages or profiles you visited, your IP address, the type of web browser and operating system used, and the address of any website that directed you to the Services. Blog Ninja may collect and aggregate usage information related to your use of the Services. 

We may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), or other similar technology in connection with your use of the Services (collectively, "Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Services, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. You can disable some (but not all) Cookies in your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the services provided through the Services. 

**Third-Party Vendors and Advertisers.** Blog Ninja may use third-party vendors, to collect and analyze information about your use of the Services. These vendors may include Google or other third-parties. These third-parties may use cookies or other similar mechanisms to provide us with information and analysis about your use of the Services. This information collection and analysis allows us to better understand how the Services are being used so that we can strive to provide the most relevant content to our users. This information may also be used to serve interest-based advertisements on our website or other websites across the internet. 

Blog Ninja may, from time to time, use one or more of the following Google analytics features: AdWords, Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We may combine information gathered from one or more of these services. 

For information on how Google collects and uses the information collected through Blog Ninja's use of the Google analytics and advertising services, see the Google, Inc. Privacy Policy here (https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). 

For more information about the Google analytics features used by Blog Ninja, click here (https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2404395?hl=en&ref_topic=1631776&rd=1). 

For information on how to see and change your Google Ad Settings, click here (https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662856?hl=en). 

For information on the use of the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On, click here (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). However, Blog Ninja does not necessarily endorse this add-on and does not guarantee that using the add-on will be effective. 

Blog Ninja does not guarantee that it will take action in response to all do-not-track signals or similar mechanisms. Additionally, some third-party service providers may still collect tracking information even if you have enabled your browser's do-not-track functionality or utilized a similar do-not-track mechanism. 

**INFORMATION USE PRACTICES**

Blog Ninja may use the collected information or data described above, individually or in the aggregate, for any lawful purpose, including, but not limited to, such purposes as analyzing and tracking the level or type of user activity on the Services, tracking and analyzing usage trends, tracking a person's online browsing habits, personalizing the Services to better reflect your preferences, serving more relevant advertisements, or enhancing your and other users' use of the Services. 

**Blog Ninja may also use your submitted information to contact you, via regular mail, email, text message, telephone, or otherwise, regarding your account, the Services, or other relevant or promotional information as determined by Blog Ninja or its partners.**

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

Blog Ninja may disclose, sell, or transfer any collected information to third-parties for any lawful purpose in our sole discretion. 

Blog Ninja may use third-party companies, agents, or contractors to perform services on our behalf. For example, Blog Ninja may partner with other companies to personalize our web pages, analyze our website or usage information, process credit card transactions, collect debts, analyze or enhance the data collected by the Services (including user's interaction with the Services), or otherwise assist Blog Ninja in better serving the Services' users. During the course of providing Blog Ninja with these services, these third-parties may have access to your personal and non-personal information. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them. 

Blog Ninja may disclose your information to third-parties for marketing purposes. These third-parties may contact you via any method of contact you provide to Blog Ninja. 

Blog Ninja also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety. 

In the event that Blog Ninja is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right, to sell or otherwise transfer any and all information we have collected from you as part of that transaction and such third party will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Policy. 

**THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

The Services may contain links to websites not owned or controlled by Blog Ninja. Blog Ninja does not necessarily review or endorse the content of these linked websites. You should review the terms of service and privacy policies of all websites you visit. 

**SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information we collect on the Services. Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% effective. Accordingly, we cannot absolutely guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. You are responsible for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access the Services. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to our Services. By using the Services, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of these Services. 

**DATA RETENTION**

Blog Ninja may retain the personal and non-personal information or other collected data, individually or in the aggregate, as described above, after you delete your account. However, Blog Ninja does not guarantee that any information will continue to be available after such deletion. 

**VIEWING AND UPDATING INFORMATION**

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the accuracy of your personal information that you provide to or through the Services. If you would like to update your contact information, you may do so by visiting your account page on the Services or contacting Blog Ninja at the address below. If you believe you have submitted inaccurate information through the Services, and would like Blog Ninja to change such information, please contact Blog Ninja at the address below. 

**CONTACT**

If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please contact Blog Ninja at the following address: 

**Blog Ninja**   
**1316 N. Street**   
**Lincoln, NE   68508**
